IFSCL故事模式
动画预告
第二十章 - 剧情画面
烟花
临时音乐: Lovely Complex - Dry Tears
( 请打开字幕 )
IFSCL故事模式 - 早期动画 - "烟花" (WIP = Work In Progress，意为制作中)
注意2018-07-14是法国的节日，法国国庆节
该视频更新的日期为2018-07-13
英文字幕: 原版字幕
翻译，压制: Bolshevik0
Jeremy: You were right, I needed some air…
Jeremy: 你说的没错 我需要出来走走
Jeremy: Hey... Is something wrong?
Jeremy: 嘿 怎么了
Jeremy: I'm sorry I haven't payed much attention lately.
Jeremy: 很抱歉我之前都没注意到
Aelita: No... It's not your fault. I... I'm sorry.
Aelita: 不 这不是你的错 对不起
Aelita: Everytime I look at the full moon, I start to cry.
Aelita: 每当我看到月亮的时候 我都止不住地哭
Aelita: I don't know why...
Aelita: 我不知道为什么
Jeremy: But... why did you bring me here if it makes you cry?
Jeremy: 但是 为什么你要带我来一个让你哭的地方
Aelita: I didn't bring you here for the moon.
Aelita: 我带你来不是为了看月亮
Jeremy: Really?
Jeremy: 真的吗
Jeremy: Why are we going on the roof then?
Jeremy: 为什么我们要到屋顶上
Aelita: You'll see very soon.
Aelita: 你很快就会知道
Jeremy: Fireworks... Of course! It's the 14th of July...
Jeremy: 烟花……正因为今天是7月14日
Jeremy: I completely forgot. What day it was.
Jeremy: 我完全忘了今天什么日子
Aelita: That's the Eiffel tower over there, right? I didn't notice it last time!
Aelita: 那儿是埃菲尔铁塔对吧 我上次甚至都没注意到
Aelita: The view must be amazing from up there...
Aelita: 那里看烟花的角度一定棒极了
Jeremy: I leave it to the tourists. I prefer our good old factory.
Jeremy: 让游客们去那里吧 我更喜欢我们亲爱的老工厂
Jeremy: I have so many memories here. It changed my life for good...
Jeremy: 我在这的回忆太多了 这里永远地改变了我的一生
Aelita: ... You changed my life too.
Aelita: ……你也永远地改变了我的一生
Aelita: I don't think I'll ever be able to thank you enough for that.
Aelita: 我觉得我怎么做都无法回报你
Jeremy: I feel the same.
Jeremy: 同感
Jeremy: It wasn't the factory that changed my life...
Jeremy: 并不是工厂改变了我
Jeremy: ...But more what I found inside, I mean who I...
Jeremy: 但是当我仔细思考这内在原因的时候……我的意思是那个我……
Jeremy原版法语&英语配音
确认参与制作
在一年内下一阶段的剧情画面制作中再见